scenekids.com 2017-03-19

# Privacy Policy - SceneKids

## Your Data

We take privacy seriously and respect the privacy of our users and the privacy of their data. All user information contained within the Site you may provide are governed by our Terms of Service. Although we own the data storage, databases and the Site itself, **you retain all rights to your data**.

## What We Collect

We collect the email addresses and certain personally identifiable information of those who communicate with us via email or register with us to open an account. We also collect certain aggregate information regarding with pages users access of visit, and information volunteered by the users (such as any surveys we may conduct and/or site registrations).

When you register on the Site we ask for the following information: email address, gender, date of birth, country, city/town and ZIP/postal code. Users of the Site also have the option to provide additional information to further personalize their account.

When you submit information, you are transferring such information into the United States of America and you hereby consent to such transfer.

We may also collect and analyze from visitors and users certain information regarding the use of the Site and services available therein. Information collection but include but it not limit to website traffic volume, frequency of visits, type and time of interactions, type of browser and operation system, et cetera.

## Use of Information

We may use personal information to provide the contents of your personal public profile on the Site. We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve the Site. We may use third-parties to assist us in processing your personal information, and we require that such third-parties comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. We may use certain other information collected from you to help diagnose technical issues, administer the Site and improve the quality and types of services delivered. We may provide non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information derived from the action of our visitors and account holders to third-parties in order to demonstrate the value we deliver to users.

The information we collect is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  1. If it becomes necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.
  2. If we or the Site is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are required to use the Site. We use cookies to assist in delivering the Service and to provide a positive and personalized user experience. Our persistent and session ID cookies are used to identify unique visitors to our sites and to provide you with easy access to your files. If you have your browser set to reject cookies, your usage of the Site is likely to be interrupted.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to this website. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visits to this site and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Security

We have implemented processes intended to protect user information and maintain security of data. Each account holder is assigned a unique user name and password, which is required to access their account. It is each user’s responsibility to protect the security of his or her login information. We have attempted to protect our servers by locating them areas with security procedures, using of firewalls and implementing other generally available security technologies.

These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of data, but NO GUARANTEE CAN BE MADE THAT YOUR INFORMATION AND DATA WILL BE SECURE FROM INTRUSIONS AND UNAUTHORIZED RELEASE TO THIRD PARTIES.

## Cancellation or Account Termination

If you choose to cancel your account and leave the Site or your account is terminated because of your breach of the Terms of Service, please be aware that we may for a time retain residual information in our backup and/or archival copies of our database. We will make reasonable commercial efforts to delete your information as soon as reasonably practical.

## Compliance with Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act

In addition to email address, we require you to provide your birth date during the registration process. We ask for your date of birth to verify that you are 13 or older, and so that we can better limit your access to content and advertisements that are not age appropriate. Falsifying said information is a violation of our Terms of Service.

## Accessing and Updating Personal Information

When you use the Site, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate purposes. You may update your account information by logging into your account. When requests come to us in regard to personal information, we ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

## Changes to this Policy

We may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by posting a prominent notice on the Site and possibly sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account. We do not intend to reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Each version of this Policy will be identified at the bottom of the page by its effective date.

## Questions or Concerns

Any questions abouts or concerns with this Privacy Policy should be addressed to [support@scenekids.com](mailto:support@scenekids.com)

## Updated: June 4th, 2011
